ALADE-RAJI FAR'HAH AYODEJI

Frontend Developer

1, Eleshin Street, Popo-Oba Square, Epe, Lagos. Lagos, Nigeria (234) 07036548910, (234) 07068043314 ibiwunmi887@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a final year student of the Electronic and Computer Engineering department of Lagos State University skilled with leadership experience and lover of teamwork. I am currently leaning towards web development with more focus on Frontend development. Currently working with HTML, CSS and a little Javascript with basic knowledge in Bootstrap. Looking forward to improving my skills in the above mentioned technologies and adding more to them to provide outstanding solutions to problems.

EXPERIENCE

Zuri, Nigeria — Intern

March 2021 - Till Date

Learning more about web development at this organization with highly skilled mentors to help boost my knowledge in everything frontend and web development.

VOLUNTEERING ACTIVITIES

Society of Petroleum Engineers, Nigeria — President

September 2020 - Present

President of the Student Chapter body of Lagos State University under the Nigeria Council branch of SPE. Here I am tasked with leading a team to help student members of the above society bridge the gap between the student chapter and the nigeria council as well as the lagos section. Also assist them in navigating the oil and gas industry by organizing several ambassador lecturer programs (ALP) that sees speakers from the industry sharing the roadmap and guidelines to successfully navigate the industry.

Society of Petroleum Engineers, Nigeria— Communications Chair

August 2019- September 2020

Communications Chair of the Student Chapter body of Lagos State University under the Nigeria Council branch of SPE. As a communications

SKILLS

Web Development

Management

Leadership

Communication

SOCIAL HANDLES

Twitter:

https://twitter.com/Reehah Rai

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/reehahrai/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ far-hah-ayodeji-alade-raji-5 34649171/

Github:

https://github.com/Reehah

LANGUAGES

English, Yoruba

Chair (P.R.O) I was tasked with disseminating first hand information to students as well as managing the social accounts of the students chapter.

Society of Petroleum Engineers — Short Course Committee Member

July 2020 - August 2020

An Energy Industry Transformation Summit was organized by the Society of Petroleum Engineers, Nigerian Council. The summit featured plenary sessions, short courses and lots of networking. I happened to work as a committee member on the short courses. I was privileged to Co host one of the short courses titled "Process Safety and Asset Integrity Management" alongside the facilitators. It was a different experience for me and a really nice one.

Lagos State University, Epe, Lagos — Team Lead, The Leadership Conference 2019

May 2019 - July 2019

I was saddled with the responsibility of building a team of hardworking people to organize a leadership conference with the aim of imbibing and inculcating leadership skills no matter how little in students and members of the campus. This event featured leaders in different fields sharing their various diversified knowledge with members of Epe Campus.

Society of Petroleum Engineers, Nigeria — Host

August 2019 - Till Date

I have hosted several webinars for the Lagos State University students chapter, SPE Lagos Section and SPE Nigeria Council.

EDUCATION

Queen's College, Yaba, Lagos — SSCE.

September 2011 - August 2014

Lagos State University, Epe, Lagos — BSc. Electronic and Computer Engineering.

December 2015 - Till Date

PROJECTS

Mart — https://mart-main.netlify.app/

Created a simple web page with basic knowledge of pure HTML and CSS. (Desktop View)

Ngoding — https://ngoding.netlify.app/

Created a banner page with basic knowledge of pure HTML and CSS. (Desktop View)

MEETi — https://meeti.netlify.app/

Implemented a figma design using Bootstrap.

HOBBIES

Eating, Sports, Seeing movies, Window Shopping (Online and Offline), Playing games, Open to learning new things especially new approa, Playing with kids, Reading.